# MUNKHTUR GALBADRAKH

+61 405674100

gmunkhtur@gmail.com



70/9 Broome St, Waterloo, NSW 2017

## Career objectives

Quality-oriented Computer Information Systems major currently attending Kent Institute. Aiming to leverage proven analytical, multitasking, and problem-solving skills to successfully fill the Web Developer role at your company. Frequently praised as detailoriented by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals. Although I don't have professional experience in the field, gathered experience working with team towards certain objectives in hospitality.

### EDUCATION

#### KENT INSTITUTE

Sydney, NSW

Bachelor of Information Technology Computer Information Systems Candidate (Expected graduation Jul 2020)

Relevant Coursework

Database design and development

### SKILLS

HTML/CSS/JavaScript/ES6

Nodeis/React/Express

MySQL/MongoDB

Git/Github

Photoshop

Windows /Linux

# Work Experience

2018 - Present

BARTENDER Criniti's, Sydney, NSW / Jan 2018 - Present

- Supervise the work of bar staff and other bartenders.
- Plan, organize, and control the operations of a cocktail lounge or bar.

2011 - 2014

MANAGER Piola, Arlington, VA / Apr 2011 - Feb 2014

- Ensure smooth operation of the restaurant
- Manage employee service level on shift